(Sheldon:)in this relationship
than you are.
(Sheldon:)And second...
(Sheldon:)the reason I may not be
progressing in my research is
(Sheldon:)I've created too pleasant
of an environment for myself.
(Howard:)What do you mean?
(Sheldon:)According to a classic
psychological experiment
(Sheldon:)by Yerkes and Dodson, in order
to maximize performance,
(Sheldon:)one must create a state
of productive anxiety.
(Sheldon:)So I'd like to ask you all
to do something for me.
(Sheldon:)Keep me on my toes.
(stammers)
Just throw me off my game.
E-Essentially, go out of your
way to make my life miserable.
(Howard:)Hold on.
(Howard:)What's in it for us?
(Sheldon:)Well, I suppose...
Okay, we'll do it!
(Penny:)Done.
(Amy:)33 seconds.
(Amy:)Okay, that'll be
our baseline.
(Sheldon:)You know, I don't
want to tell you